<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Plant me Green</title>
    <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Plant me Green</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://plantmegreen.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://plantmegreen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Peperomia Obtusifolia Care and Propagation: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-marble-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-marble-green/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss everything you need to know about the care and propagation of Peperomia Obtusifolia. This beautiful and easy-to-grow houseplant has rubber-like leaves that resemble mini versions of the ficus elastica, commonly known as the rubber tree. Peperomia Obtusifolia is a fast-growing plant that stays relatively small, making it a perfect addition to any indoor garden. We will cover various aspects of its care, including lighting requirements, watering needs, fertilization, and propagation methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cold Hardy Persimmon Varieties: A Guide to Choosing the Right Rootstock and Varieties</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardy-persimmon-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardy-persimmon-trees/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When it comes to persimmons, it&amp;rsquo;s important to choose the right rootstock and varieties for your specific needs. In this article, we will discuss the significance of grafting persimmons on American persimmon rootstock, the different varieties of cold-hardy persimmons available, and reputable nurseries where you can find these varieties. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned gardener or just starting out, this guide will provide you with valuable information to help you make informed decisions when it comes to growing persimmon trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Prevent Ice from Damaging Trees: Managing Ice-Storm Damaged Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-prevent-ice-from-damaging-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-prevent-ice-from-damaging-trees/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Ice storms can be devastating to trees, especially when they occur early in the season with a lot of green leaves still on the branches. The weight of the ice can cause significant damage and breakage to the tree canopy. In this article, we will discuss the steps to prevent ice damage to trees and how to manage trees that have been damaged by ice storms.
Preventing Ice Damage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PAW Patrol Hero Pups to the Rescue! Liberty, Skye &amp; Everest Save the Day | 30 Minute Compilation | Nick Jr.</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/paw-pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/paw-pot/</guid>
      <description>An Exciting Adventure with the PAW Patrol Pups In this thrilling 30-minute compilation video, the PAW Patrol team embarks on exciting missions to save the day. Join Liberty, Skye, Everest, and the rest of the fearless pups as they rescue those in need and overcome various challenges. With their bravery and teamwork, there&amp;rsquo;s no problem too big for these hero pups to handle!
Key Points Benny&amp;rsquo;s Rescue: Benny the bunny finds himself in a dangerous situation in the city, but with the help of Liberty, he is brought back to the safety of the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Syngonium Podophyllum Care and Propagation: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-white-butterfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-white-butterfly/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the care tips and propagation techniques for the popular houseplant Syngonium Podophyllum, commonly known as the White Butterfly. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or experienced plant enthusiast, this guide will provide you with all the information you need to successfully care for and propagate this beautiful plant.
Care Tips for Syngonium Podophyllum Sunlight Requirements: Syngonium Podophyllum can tolerate medium to direct sunlight, but it should avoid full sun as it can cause the leaves to burn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is Quarter Sawn Lumber?: Exploring the Beautiful Patterns in Woodworking Projects</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/width-sorted-white-oak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/width-sorted-white-oak/</guid>
      <description>Woodworking enthusiasts are often fascinated by the intricate patterns found in certain types of wood, such as white oak and leopard wood. These patterns, known as ray flaking, add a unique touch to custom woodworking projects. In this article, we will delve into the world of quarter sawn lumber, understand how it is cut, and learn some finishing tricks to bring out the best in these beautiful woods.
From Logs to Lumber: The Process of Quarter Sawn Before we can appreciate quarter sawn lumber, we need to understand the sawing process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What Is The Best Variety Of Persimmon Tree To Grow For Backyard Gardens?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-farm-in-albama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-farm-in-albama/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to another article from Plant Abundance! In this article, we will explore the best variety of persimmon tree to grow in your backyard garden. Persimmons are a delicious fruit that can be grown in USDA climate zones seven through nine. Today, we will focus on a specific variety called Jiro or Gyro Fuyu Persimmon. This variety is highly sought after by gardeners and growers due to its abundance and unique characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Empire Of The Sun - High And Low (Official Video)**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/sun-high-peach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/sun-high-peach/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will be discussing the official video for &amp;ldquo;High And Low&amp;rdquo; by Empire Of The Sun. Empire Of The Sun is known for their unique blend of electronic and alternative rock music. The song &amp;ldquo;High And Low&amp;rdquo; is a captivating track that takes listeners on a nostalgic journey through the complexities of life and love. In this article, we will analyze the lyrics, explore the meaning behind the song, and delve into the visual elements of the official video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fertilizing Figs for Maximum Production: Double Your Fig Harvest</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/best-fertilizer-for-fig-trees-to-get-fruit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/best-fertilizer-for-fig-trees-to-get-fruit/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
If you want to increase your fig tree&amp;rsquo;s production and overall yield, then this article is for you. In this video transcript, we will discuss the best fertilizers for fig trees to ensure maximum fruit production. Timing and the right method are crucial when it comes to fertilizing fig trees, and following the steps outlined here can dramatically increase your fig harvest. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and learn how to optimize the fertilizing process for your fig trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pin Oak (Quercus palustris) - The Ideal Landscape Tree for American Gardens</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/green-pin-oaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/green-pin-oaks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Oaks are an integral part of the American landscape, gracing neighborhoods, old towns, and city parks alike. Among the many oak species used in landscaping throughout North America, one particularly popular choice is the Pin Oak (Quercus palustris). In this article, we will explore the unique characteristics of the Pin Oak, its identification features, and why it is an excellent choice for your garden. So, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the world of Pin Oaks and discover why they are such a beloved addition to any green space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don&#39;t Make These 7 Mistakes in the Blueberry Growing Process: A Guide to Successful Blueberry Cultivation</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ochlockonee-blueberry-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ochlockonee-blueberry-bush/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries are a delicious and nutritious fruit that are relatively easy to grow. However, in order to achieve success with your blueberry bushes, it is important to avoid certain common mistakes. In this article, we will discuss the seven crucial mistakes to avoid when planting and growing blueberries.
Choosing the Right Varieties for Your Growing Zone The first mistake many people make when planting blueberries is not selecting the appropriate varieties for their specific growing zone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Prevent Corn from Blowing Over: Tips and Techniques</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/stop-wind-from-blowing-plants-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/stop-wind-from-blowing-plants-over/</guid>
      <description>Corn plants are known for their tall and slender stalks, but they can be prone to blowing over in strong winds. If you&amp;rsquo;re a gardener who has faced this issue every year, you may be wondering how to keep your corn from toppling over. In this article, we will discuss some helpful tips and techniques to prevent your corn plants from blowing over and ensure a successful harvest.
Key Points: Row Orientation: One of the first things you should consider is changing the orientation of your corn rows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Parallel Peperomia Tetragona Puteolata Propagation: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-puteolata-propagation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-puteolata-propagation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the process of propagating Parallel Peperomia Tetragona Puteolata, a popular type of houseplant. Peperomia Puteolata, also known as Parallel Peperomia or Parallel Stem Peperomia, is a trailing plant with unique parallel stems and heart-shaped leaves. Propagation is a great way to expand your plant collection or share plants with others. We will provide a detailed step-by-step guide on how to propagate this fascinating plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Blueberries Really Blue? The Truth Behind the Color of Blueberries</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/blueberries-are-not-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/blueberries-are-not-blue/</guid>
      <description>Introduction During the holiday season, many families come together to celebrate and enjoy delicious meals. However, sometimes unexpected dietary restrictions can present a challenge, as Randy Felt-Face discovered when his cousin called to discuss her son&amp;rsquo;s inability to eat blue foods. In this article, we will explore the truth behind the color of blueberries and why they might not actually be as blue as you think.
The Curious Case of Brayden Randy&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s son, Brayden, has a peculiar condition where he cannot consume foods that contain a blue food preservative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Profitable Pecans: Capitalizing on Increased Demand in South Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecans-for-sale-in-south-arkansas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecans-for-sale-in-south-arkansas/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In recent years, pecan growers in Arkansas and the United States have been experiencing a profitable environment, thanks to the increased demand from China and the traditional holiday market. This surge has offered significant financial opportunities to farmers, such as Robert Carruthers, who owns a 165-acre orchard in the beautiful Arkansas River Valley of Conway County. By understanding the dynamics of the market and leveraging key advantages like irrigation, Carruthers has been able to maximize his pecan production and reap the benefits of rising prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **How to Prune a Peach Tree in 4 Simple Steps for Maximum Production**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/tropic-zest-peach-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/tropic-zest-peach-tree/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to growing peach trees, pruning is an essential practice that can greatly impact the health and productivity of the tree. In this article, we will discuss the proper technique for pruning a peach tree to maximize fruit production. By following these 4 simple steps, you can ensure that your peach tree bears large, healthy fruit and remains less susceptible to disease.
Step 1: Understand the Best Shape for Peach Trees Before you start pruning your peach tree, it is important to understand the most productive shape for peaches to grow in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 8 Garden Fails This Year: Reflecting on the Ups and Downs of Gardening</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/8-arborvitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/8-arborvitae/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Gardening is a rewarding and fulfilling hobby, but it&amp;rsquo;s not without its challenges. In this article, we will take a closer look at eight garden fails that the Garden Answer channel experienced this year. From mysterious plant deaths to poor planning, these garden fails serve as a reminder that even experts face setbacks. Join us as we explore each fail in detail and discuss potential solutions.
1. The Mystery of the Dying Arborvitaes The first garden fail revolves around a row of arborvitaes behind the greenhouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sweet Magnolias Season 3: A Tale of New Relationships and Self-Discovery</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/little-magnolias/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/little-magnolias/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the official trailer for Sweet Magnolias Season 3, released by Netflix, we are introduced to a story that centers around friendship, love, and the challenges faced by a group of old friends. The trailer takes us on an emotional journey, showcasing the characters&amp;rsquo; personal struggles and their quest for self-discovery. This article will delve into the key points brought up in the trailer, highlighting the themes of the series and the characters&amp;rsquo; individual arcs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 10 Best Flowering Trees for Your Front Yard</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardiness-zone-4-flowering-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardiness-zone-4-flowering-tree/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to beautify your front yard with vibrant colors and fragrant blooms? Look no further than the stunning world of flowering trees. These majestic trees not only add shape and color to your residential landscape but also provide shade and attract birds with their clusters of flowers and berries. In this article, we will explore the top 10 flowering trees that will transform your front yard into a delightful spectacle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Persimmon Fruit Drop: Understanding the Role of Persimmon Psyllid</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-flower-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-flower-drop/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the phenomenon of persimmon fruit drop, shedding light on the various theories and factors that contribute to this common issue among persimmon trees. As an expert gardener with extensive experience in cultivating persimmon trees, Ross Raddi shares his insights and observations regarding fruit drop, with a particular focus on the potential role of the persimmon psyllid.
Understanding Persimmon Fruit Drop Persimmon trees are notorious for shedding their fruits, even in cases where the trees are well-established and cared for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Care for Scindapsus Pictus: Top Tips for Healthy and Flourishing Plants 🌿 </title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/scindapsus-pictus-exotica-plant-moss-pole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/scindapsus-pictus-exotica-plant-moss-pole/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss everything you need to know about caring for Scindapsus Pictus plants. Scindapsus Pictus, also known as the Velvet Leaf plant, is a popular houseplant with beautiful, velvety leaves. In this video transcript, we will cover the key points for keeping your Scindapsus Pictus plants happy and healthy, from lighting and watering requirements to cleaning and fertilizing tips.
Lighting Requirements Scindapsus Pictus plants are known for their adaptability to lower lighting conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Persimmon, Asian Pear, and Fig Tree Winter Order Unboxing and Planting in the UK</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pear-fig-persimmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pear-fig-persimmon/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Lyonheart84&amp;rsquo;s exotic fruit growing channel. In this video, we will be unboxing and planting persimmon, Asian pear, and fig tree orders that arrived in the UK. Stay tuned as we explore the different varieties and discuss their winter care.
Unboxing and Examining the Plants On a sunny day in January 2018, Lyonheart84 received a box of plants which had arrived on Friday. These plants were a Christmas present from his parents, with a few persimmons and fig plants inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ginny Peperomia Care: Easy Steps to Thrive in Bright Indoor Light</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-ginny-light-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-ginny-light-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Peperomias are unique and beautiful plants that add a touch of green to any space. In this article, we will focus on the Ginny Peperomia, a species that originates from the South American rainforest. This plant thrives in bright light but can be sensitive to direct sunlight. We will explore the ideal light requirements for Ginny Peperomia, as well as its watering needs and repotting guidelines.
Light Requirements for Ginny Peperomia Ginny Peperomias naturally grow under the canopies of trees in the rainforest, so they prefer bright but indirect light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pecan Grafting Wood for Sale: A Comprehensive Guide on Collection and Growth</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-grafting-wood-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-grafting-wood-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pecan grafting is a popular technique used by horticulturists and gardeners to propagate pecan trees. In order to successfully graft pecan trees, it is crucial to collect high-quality pecan scion wood. In this article, we will discuss the process of collecting pecan scion wood and provide detailed information on the different sizes and qualities of scion wood. Whether you are a commercial grower or a home gardener, understanding the best practices for collecting and using pecan scion wood is essential for successful grafting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Discover the Aesthetic Charm and Health Benefits of Jester&#39;s Crown Fern as an Indoor Plant</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/jester-fern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/jester-fern/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Incorporating indoor plants into your home not only adds a touch of natural beauty but also offers numerous health benefits. One such plant that can bring elegance and tranquility to your indoor space is the Jester&amp;rsquo;s Crown Fern, scientifically known as Nephrolepis exaltata var. tenuisecta &amp;lsquo;Gold&amp;rsquo;. This remarkable fern not only enhances the aesthetic appeal of your living space but also acts as an air purifier, improves indoor air quality, and promotes relaxation and mindfulness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Successfully Grow Pecan Trees: A Comprehensive Guide by Hawkins Corner</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/caddo-pecan-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/caddo-pecan-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you interested in growing your very own pecan trees? Pecan trees are a popular choice due to their delicious nuts and the beauty they add to any landscape. However, it’s important to note that not all pecan trees are created equal. In this article, we will guide you through the process of growing pecan trees, ensuring that you choose the right type of tree and provide it with the necessary care it needs to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pawpaw&#39;s Pecans: The Finest Pecans for Sale in Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecans-for-sale-in-arkansas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecans-for-sale-in-arkansas/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of delicious, high-quality pecans? Look no further than Pawpaw&amp;rsquo;s Pecans, located on the beautiful Charlotte Theresa plantation in Arkansas. Not only can you find the finest pecans here, but you can also enjoy a charming bed and breakfast experience. In this article, we will dive into the fascinating history of the pecan industry and explore the journey of Pawpaw&amp;rsquo;s Pecans. Get ready to discover why these pecans are a must-have for your holiday treats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Salavatski Pomegranate: A Taste of Russian Excellence</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/salavatski-pomegranate-taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/salavatski-pomegranate-taste/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article is based on a Youtube transcript titled &amp;ldquo;Russian Pomegranate – FutureOfFlavor.&amp;rdquo; It has been rewritten for SEO purposes and to provide a comprehensive understanding of the topic.
Introduction In front of us stands a remarkable pomegranate known as the Salavatski. This specific variety was cultivated in Turkmenistan by Dr. Levin, a passionate fruit enthusiast and breeder who worked at an experiment station in the former USSR. Over a span of 40 years, he dedicated himself to perfecting 1,400 distinct varieties of pomegranates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> String of Fishhooks: Care Instructions for a Drought-Tolerant Succulent Plant</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/string-of-fish-hooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/string-of-fish-hooks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the care instructions for a succulent plant called the string of fish hooks, also known as Sinacia radicans. This unique plant is known for its ability to store backup moisture in its succulent leaves, making it drought-tolerant. We will go over the ideal light conditions, proper trimming techniques, and specific watering instructions to ensure the health and longevity of your string of fish hooks plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Olympian Hardy Fig: A Peach-Flavored Delight for Your Garden**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/olympian-hardy-fig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/olympian-hardy-fig/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a delicious and hardy addition to your garden? Look no further than the Olympian Hardy Fig. This large, peach-flavored fig tree is a true gem for any gardener. In this article, we will discuss the characteristics of the Olympian Fig and why it is a great option for your garden. We will also go over the taste test results and provide some insights on how to care for this tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Fertilize Magnolias: Optimizing Nutrient Levels for Little Gem Magnolia Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/nutrients-for-magnolia-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/nutrients-for-magnolia-trees/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Magnolias are beautiful trees known for their vibrant flowers and glossy green foliage. To ensure healthy growth and abundant flowering, it is crucial to provide these trees with the right nutrients. In this article, we will discuss the best fertilization practices for magnolia trees, with a focus on the popular Little Gem variety. By understanding the importance of soil pH, choosing the right fertilizer, and implementing proper fertilization techniques, you can promote optimal growth and maximize the beauty of your magnolia trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> This Guy Takes the Plunge and Tries Fruit for the First Time Ever</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pineapple-pear-strawberry-fist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pineapple-pear-strawberry-fist/</guid>
      <description>Are you someone who has always turned up your nose at the sight of fruit? Is the thought of trying a piece of fruit terrifying to you? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Meet Ryan, a self-proclaimed fruit hater who has never eaten fruit in his entire life. In a quest to improve his health and appearance, Ryan is determined to overcome his fear and give fruit a chance.
Conquering Fear, One Fruit at a Time As the video starts, Ryan admits that his parents have tried countless times to get him to eat fruit, but he has always vehemently refused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Dig Up and Transplant a Crepe Myrtle: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-dig-up-a-crepe-myrtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-dig-up-a-crepe-myrtle/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you interested in learning how to dig up and transplant a Crepe Myrtle? In this article, we will provide you with a step-by-step guide on how to successfully transplant a Crepe Myrtle and even split it into multiple trees. Transplanting a Crepe Myrtle can be a challenging task, but with the right knowledge and techniques, you can turn a single tree into two or three beautiful ones. So, grab your gardening tools and let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tree&#39;s Sacrifice: A Story of Friendship and Unconditional Love of Nature</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/story-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/story-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the peaceful outskirts of a city, there stood a tall and vibrant tree. With its long branches and countless green leaves, it was a sight to behold. Birds from faraway places would come to sit on its branches and fill the forest with their melodious songs. This tree had a special bond with a young boy from a nearby town. They would spend hours together, sharing their dreams and laughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Raintree Fruit Feature: Melrose Apple - A Juicy and Sweet Flavor Sensation**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/melrose-apple-picking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/melrose-apple-picking/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Welcome to Raintree Nursery! In this article, we are going to explore the marvelous Melrose apple, a variety that has captured the hearts of apple enthusiasts everywhere. With its unbelievable flavor, excellent storage capabilities, and resistance to cedar apple rust, this apple is truly a gem. Join us as we delve into the characteristics and qualities that make Melrose a standout choice for apple lovers.
The Flavorful Delight of Melrose Apple: Melrose apple, a cross between Jonathan and Red Delicious, boasts an incredible flavor profile that is sure to impress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shaw Maple Blaze Flooring: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/shaw-maple-blaze-flooring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/shaw-maple-blaze-flooring/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the Shaw Maple Blaze Flooring, a popular choice for homeowners looking for a durable and stylish flooring option. We will go over the key features of this flooring, its installation process, and provide an honest review based on our own experience. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering Shaw Maple Blaze Flooring for your home, this article is a must-read!
Key Points Here are the key points we will be covering in this article:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alocasia Bambino Care and Propagation: A Guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/alocasia-bambino/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/alocasia-bambino/</guid>
      <description>The Alocasia Bambino, also known as the dwarf version of the Alocasia Amazonica, is a beautiful and popular plant that is relatively easy to care for and propagate. In this article, we will explore the key points of caring for and propagating Alocasia Bambino, providing step-by-step instructions and tips for success.
Understanding Alocasia Bambino The Alocasia Bambino is a compact plant with narrow, interestingly shaped leaves that converge into a more narrow shape at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Janet Craig Compacta: A Stylish and Low Maintenance Plant for Any Space</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/janet-craig-does-not-bloom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/janet-craig-does-not-bloom/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a stylish and low maintenance plant to add to your indoor space? Look no further than the Janet Craig Compacta. This plant, part of the Janet Craig line, is known for its ability to thrive in low light conditions while maintaining its unique and cool shape. In this article, we will explore the different forms and sizes of the Janet Craig Compacta, as well as its care requirements and maintenance tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Peperomia &#39;Ginny&#39;: The Perfect Easy-to-Care Houseplant - Martin&#39;s Home &amp; Garden</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-ginny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-ginny/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a beautiful and low-maintenance houseplant? Look no further than Peperomia &amp;lsquo;Ginny&amp;rsquo;! This stunning plant, also known as Red Edge Peperomia, Tricolor Peperomia, or Rainbow Peperomia, is the star of this week&amp;rsquo;s edition of Martin&amp;rsquo;s Houseplant of the Week. With its attractive foliage and ease of care, Peperomia &amp;lsquo;Ginny&amp;rsquo; is a great addition to any indoor space.
Why Peperomia &amp;lsquo;Ginny&amp;rsquo;? One of the reasons why Peperomia &amp;lsquo;Ginny&amp;rsquo; is so popular among plant enthusiasts is its non-toxicity to pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Tour of Pink Satin Pomegranates at Dave Wilson Nursery</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pink-satin-pomegranate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pink-satin-pomegranate/</guid>
      <description>Pomegranates are a delicious and refreshing fruit that are known for their bold flavor and nutritional benefits. In this article, we will take a virtual tour of the pink satin pomegranates at Dave Wilson Nursery and explore the different varieties and flavors they offer.
The Germ Plasm Collection: One of the main highlights of this tour is the visit to the Germ Plasm Collection of pomegranates at Dave Wilson Nursery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Don&#39;t EVER Rake Leaves Again! Leaf Mulch Improves Your Soil &amp; Fertilizes The Yard | How To Tutorial**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/magnolia-leaves-mulch-to-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/magnolia-leaves-mulch-to-big/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the benefits of using leaf mulch instead of raking leaves from your lawn. We often view the act of raking leaves as a necessary chore to maintain cleanliness, but in reality, it is a wasteful and unnecessary practice. By using leaves as natural fertilizer, you can improve your soil&amp;rsquo;s fertility and promote biodiversity in your yard. We will explore the step-by-step process of utilizing leaf mulch and how it can transform your gardening practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Splitting Oak Logs: A Step-by-Step Process with a 30 Ton Northstar Hydraulic Splitter on a 14 ft Suretrac Trailer</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/14-ft-life-oak-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/14-ft-life-oak-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the process of splitting oak logs using a 30 Ton Northstar hydraulic splitter. Oak logs are known for their strength and durability, making them a popular choice for firewood and woodworking projects. We will also touch on the hauling aspect, using a 14 ft Suretrac trailer. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and learn how to efficiently split oak logs.
Key Points: Introduction to Oak Logs 30 Ton Northstar Hydraulic Splitter Hauling on a 14 ft Suretrac Trailer Splitting Oak Logs Before we start splitting the oak logs, let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between two types of oak wood - red and pin oak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Taking Care of Trees in Fall in Florida: 7 Fast Producing Fruit Trees Every Floridian Needs</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/taking-care-of-trees-in-fall-in-florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/taking-care-of-trees-in-fall-in-florida/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will discuss the importance of taking care of trees in the fall season in Florida. Specifically, we will focus on seven fast-producing fruit trees that every Floridian should consider adding to their backyard or small space garden. These fruit trees are not only easy to grow but also yield delicious fruit within a year or two. We will provide detailed information about each tree, including their growing conditions, production timelines, and taste profiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Crusader Kings Family Tree: The Kingdom of Jerusalem</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/baldwin-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/baldwin-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the fascinating family tree of the Crusader Kings who embarked on a holy mission to the Middle East, specifically the Kingdom of Jerusalem. We will delve into the lives and legacies of these medieval monarchs as they defended their newly acquired lands against hostile powers in a distant and treacherous land. From heroic figures like Richard the Lionheart to controversial leaders of the Fourth Crusade, we will uncover their stories and understand the intricacies of the Kingdom of Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The 2 Easiest Fruit Trees for Beginners To Grow: Citrus and Jujube Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fast-growing-fruit-trees-virginia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fast-growing-fruit-trees-virginia/</guid>
      <description>Are you a beginner gardener looking to grow fruit trees but feeling intimidated by the process? Planting and caring for fruit trees can be daunting with the initial cost, required care, and the patience needed for fruit production. However, there are two fruit trees that stand out as the easiest to grow: citrus trees and jujube trees.
In this article, we will dive into the advantages of planting these two trees, their minimal care requirements, and their ability to thrive in various climates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Everything You Need to Know About Crab Apple Trees for Deer: A Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/crabapple-tree-for-deer-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/crabapple-tree-for-deer-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to attracting wildlife to your property, crab apple trees are an excellent choice. These native trees produce small fruits in the fall that deer absolutely love. In this article, we will explore everything you need to know about crab apple trees for deer, from their benefits to planting and care tips.
The Benefits of Crab Apple Trees for Deer Crab apple trees, especially Southern varieties, are highly popular as a food source for wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> McIntosh Family Orchard: A Legacy of Quality Summer Fruit</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/shipping-mcintosh-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/shipping-mcintosh-apples/</guid>
      <description>Introduction McIntosh Orchard, located near Alexandra, has been a prominent player in the fruit-growing industry for several generations. In this article, we will explore the history and success of McIntosh Orchard, and delve into their commitment to quality and sustainability. Join us as we uncover the story behind this thriving family-run business.
From Gold Miners to Farmers The McIntosh family first arrived in the Alexandra area during the gold rush of the 1860s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Single Trunk vs Multi-Trunk Trees: Which One Should You Pick?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/multi-trunk-vs-single-trunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/multi-trunk-vs-single-trunk/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to selecting trees for your landscape, one important decision to make is whether to choose a single trunk tree or a multi-trunk tree. Each option has its own unique characteristics and benefits that can greatly impact the overall design and functionality of your outdoor space. In this article, we will explore the differences between single trunk and multi-trunk trees, discuss their advantages and considerations, and provide guidance on which option may be best for your specific needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 13 Fruit Trees You Can Grow in Your Zone 10b Backyard</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/grow-zone-10b-fruit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/grow-zone-10b-fruit/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to grow your own fruit trees but thought it wasn&amp;rsquo;t possible in your zone 10b backyard? Think again! In this article, we will discuss 13 different fruit trees that you can successfully grow in your zone 10b backyard. From cherimoya to bananas, we will cover a wide variety of trees that will thrive in your specific climate.
1. Cherry Moya Tree
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the cherry moya tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cypress Tree History: Unveiling its Spiritual Significance in the Bible</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/cypress-tree-symbolism-bible/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/cypress-tree-symbolism-bible/</guid>
      <description>The Cypress tree, scientifically known as Cupressus sempervirens and commonly referred to as the Cypress of the Cupressaceae family, holds a rich history and spiritual significance. Originating from the East and now predominantly found in Mediterranean gardens and cemeteries, this perennial conical-shaped tree stands at a majestic height of about 28 meters or 80 feet. With its evergreen dark green foliage, small flowers, and round brown-grey cones containing seed nuts, the Cypress tree is a captivating presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Health Benefits and Facts of Native Pecans from Oklahoma</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/choctaw-pecan-tree-facts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/choctaw-pecan-tree-facts/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to crops associated with Native American tribes, most people think of the three sister crops – beans, corn, and squash. However, there is another crop that has an even longer history with indigenous people in the United States – pecans. Native pecans are found in various states, including Oklahoma, where they have been growing wild for centuries.
Native pecans thrive in riparian soils, particularly in deep and rich river bottoms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Grow Apples in Containers: A Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/can-crab-apple-trees-be-grown-in-pots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/can-crab-apple-trees-be-grown-in-pots/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Growing apple trees in containers can be a rewarding experience, especially for those who have limited garden space. In this article, we will explore the basics of growing apples in containers, including choosing the right rootstock and variety, selecting the right container, preparing the soil, and providing proper care for the tree. By following these guidelines, you can successfully grow apple trees in pots and enjoy a bountiful harvest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mandarin Plant Care &amp; Growing Tips: A Guide to the Chlorophytum Orchidastrum </title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mandarin-fire-flash-plant-temperature-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mandarin-fire-flash-plant-temperature-low/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of vibrant colors, then the Mandarin plant is sure to catch your eye. Also known as the Mandarin Spider Plant or Fire Flash, this stunning plant belongs to the genus Chlorophytum and is closely related to the popular Spider Plant. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into Mandarin plant care and provide you with all the necessary tips to help your plant thrive. From light and watering requirements to soil and repotting guidelines, this comprehensive guide will ensure that your Mandarin plant grows healthy and vibrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Our Favorite Peach Varieties for Warm Climates | Earligrande Peach Review</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/early-grande-peach-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/early-grande-peach-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Edge of Nowhere Farm, where we bring you the best fruit trees for warm climates. Today, we are excited to introduce you to our final peach variety of the season: the early grande peach. These trees have been thriving in our Arizona farm for almost two years, and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to share their beauty and deliciousness with you. Join us as we explore the unique features of the early grande peach and how it compares to other peach varieties we have grown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 17 Best Rose of Sharon Varieties: Explore the Exquisite Hibiscus Syriacus Types</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/double-purple-rose-of-sharon-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/double-purple-rose-of-sharon-tree/</guid>
      <description>Rose of Sharon, scientifically known as Hibiscus syriacus, is a magnificent flowering plant that adds a touch of elegance to any garden. With its vibrant colors and exotic blooms, it resembles a small tree that can reach impressive heights. In this article, we will explore the 17 best Rose of Sharon varieties that you should consider growing in your garden to introduce a burst of color and beauty.
1. Pink: Graceful Pastel Blooms One of the most stunning Rose of Sharon varieties is the Pink variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 10 Fruit Trees for Southern California Backyards</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/easiest-fruit-trees-to-grow-in-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/easiest-fruit-trees-to-grow-in-california/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Southern California is known for its diverse climates, ranging from subtropical to cold winter zones. With USDA hardiness Zone ratings of 5A to 11A and varying elevations, the region provides an ideal environment to grow a wide range of fruit trees. In this article, we will explore ten of the easiest fruit trees to grow in Southern California, including their unique characteristics and growing requirements.
1. Fig Trees Fig trees thrive in the southern part of California, especially in areas with a Mediterranean climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jack&#39;s Backyard: Exploring the Beauty of Crepe Myrtle in Late Summer</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/crepe-myrtle-nj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/crepe-myrtle-nj/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Discovering the Fascination of Crepe Myrtle Welcome to Al&amp;rsquo;s Garden &amp;amp; Home, where Jack Biggie takes you on a journey to explore the breathtaking beauty of crepe myrtle. With over 55 years of experience, Jack is here to share his expertise and unveil why crepe myrtle is an exceptional late summer stunner.
Unveiling the Beauty of Crepe Myrtle Crepe myrtle, also known as Lagerstroemia, is a botanical marvel that blossoms into vibrant clusters of flowers in late summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 4 Effective Methods to Protect Plants From Strong Winds</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/protect-trees-from-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/protect-trees-from-wind/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the best techniques to protect your plants from strong winds. With the proper precautions, you can minimize the risk of breakage and ensure the health and longevity of your plants, particularly fruit trees. We will explore why staking is not the ideal solution and provide alternative methods that are more effective in safeguarding your trees. Additionally, we will cover the importance of proper pruning and reducing the weight of the tree to prevent damage from high winds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mexican Plum Tree for Sale Near Me</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mexican-plum-tree-for-sale-near-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mexican-plum-tree-for-sale-near-me/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to add a beautiful and fruitful tree to your garden? Look no further than the Mexican Plum (Prunus mexicana). In this article, we will explore the features and benefits of this remarkable tree and why it is a must-have for any wildlife enthusiast or fruit lover.
Introduction to the Mexican Plum At Mossy Oak Native Nurseries, we consider the Mexican Plum to be one of our absolute favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> String of Fishhooks - Care Instructions for a Drought-Tolerant Succulent Plant</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/string-of-fishhooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/string-of-fishhooks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction String of Fishhooks, scientifically known as Senecio radicans, is a succulent plant known for its unique appearance and ability to store water in its leaves. In this article, we will discuss the care instructions for this plant, including light requirements, pruning techniques, and watering methods. Whether you are a succulent enthusiast or a beginner gardener, these tips will help you keep your String of Fishhooks thriving.
Light Requirements To ensure the optimal growth of your String of Fishhooks, it is important to provide it with the right amount of light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Syngonium Podophyllum Care and Propagation: A Guide to Growing and Propagating Syngonium Plants</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-merry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-merry/</guid>
      <description>Syngonium podophyllum, commonly known as the Syngonium or Arrowhead plant, is a popular houseplant with a variety of growth patterns and leaf patterns. In this article, we will explore the care tips for Syngonium podophyllum, discuss different types of growth and leaf patterns, and learn how to propagate these plants using various techniques.
Care Tips for Syngonium Podophyllum Sunlight Requirements Syngonium podophyllum can tolerate medium to direct sunlight, but it should be protected from full sun as it can burn the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Foot Pain Magnolia: Understanding and Treating Common Foot Conditions</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/foot-pain-magnolia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/foot-pain-magnolia/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Foot pain can be debilitating, affecting your ability to walk, run, and perform daily activities. It&amp;rsquo;s important to address foot pain promptly to prevent further complications. In this article, we will discuss common foot conditions that can cause foot pain and how to effectively treat them.
Key Points: Understanding Common Foot Conditions Identifying the Cause of Foot Pain Treatment Options for Foot Pain Prevention Measures to Maintain Healthy Feet Conclusion Understanding Common Foot Conditions Plantar Fasciitis: This condition involves inflammation of the plantar fascia, a thick band of tissue that runs along the bottom of the foot from the heel to the toes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Red Spots on Fiddle Leaf Fig Trees: Understanding and Preventing Edema</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-spots-on-fig-tree-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-spots-on-fig-tree-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss a common issue faced by plant owners - red spots or edema on the leaves of fiddle leaf fig trees. Edema, pronounced as ih-dee-ma, is the abnormal retention of water within plant cells, causing tiny red or brown spots on the new growth. These spots can be alarming to fiddle leaf fig owners, but it is important to understand that edema is a natural and harmless process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Benefits of Growing a Cold Hardy, Self-Fertile Santa Rosa Plum Tree</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/santa-rosa-plum-vs-late-santa-rosa-plum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/santa-rosa-plum-vs-late-santa-rosa-plum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the many benefits of growing a Santa Rosa plum tree. The Santa Rosa plum tree is a popular choice among gardeners in California, Arizona, and throughout the United States. This plum tree is known for its cold hardiness and self-fertility, making it a great addition to any backyard garden or food forest design.
History and Cultivation The Santa Rosa plum tree was created by Luther Burbank, an American botanist and horticulturalist, in 1906.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>  Stuewe &amp; Sons Pots: The Perfect Solution for Growing Pecan Trees in Containers</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/container-of-pecans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/container-of-pecans/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the benefits of using Stuewe &amp;amp; Sons pots for growing pecan trees in containers. Pecans are known for their deep tap roots, and it is crucial to provide them with the right conditions to thrive. Stuewe &amp;amp; Sons pots, based in Tangent, Oregon, offer a range of pots specifically designed for nursery containers. We will explore the process of growing pecan trees from seeds, the challenges involved, and how Stuewe &amp;amp; Sons pots can help overcome them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **5-in-1 Pear Tree: Growing Multiple Fruits on a Single Tree**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/5-in-1-pear-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/5-in-1-pear-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back to The Busy Gardener channel! In this article, we will explore the concept of a multi-budded tree, where different types of fruit can grow on a single tree. This unique and fascinating method allows you to have a variety of fruits in your backyard orchard. Imagine having four different types of peaches, apples, or pears, all from one tree! We will delve into the details of how this process works and its practical applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 7 Dreams Revealing Your Prophetic Gift and Biblical Dream Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-prophetic-meaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-prophetic-meaning/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we are going to discuss dreams that reveal your prophetic gift. First Corinthians 12 mentions nine spiritual gifts given to believers by the Holy Spirit, and three of these gifts are known as the knowledge gifts - the word of knowledge, the word of wisdom, and the discerning of spirits. We will focus specifically on these gifts and how they can be identified through elements and symbols in dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Air Pear by Airius: Cut Energy Costs with Thermal Destratification</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/air-pear-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/air-pear-pricing/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, where energy costs are on the rise and companies are striving to reduce carbon emissions and implement sustainable practices, finding solutions to decrease energy requirements is a top priority. The Air Pear thermal equalizer by Airius offers a range of thermal destratification fans that can help achieve this goal in any working environment.
When heating an internal space, traditional heating systems often have to over deliver in order to replace the heat that naturally rises to the ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Syngonium Podophyllum Care and Propagation: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-white-butterfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/syngonium-podophyllum-white-butterfly/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s article, we will be discussing the care and propagation of Syngonium Podophyllum, also known as the &amp;lsquo;White Butterfly&amp;rsquo; plant. We will explore the different growth patterns and leaf variations of this plant, as well as provide step-by-step instructions for propagation. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced plant lover, Syngonium Podophyllum is a forgiving and beautiful addition to any indoor garden. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Grow and Care for Peperomia Tricolor: The Perfect Perennial House Plant</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-clusiifolia-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/peperomia-clusiifolia-care/</guid>
      <description>Peperomia tricolor, also known as rainbow peperomia, guinea peppermia, jelly plant, or Ginny peperomia, is a beautiful perennial house plant that thrives in low light conditions, making it ideal for offices or desktops. In this article, we will discuss the key points to effectively grow and care for this stunning plant.
Key Points: Perfect Indoor Plant: Peperomia tricolor is an excellent choice for indoor gardening due to its ability to thrive in low light conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making Maple Jack: The Perfect Ingredient for a Festive Maple Eggnog</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/brandy-maple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/brandy-maple/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this episode of &amp;ldquo;Doin&amp;rsquo; the Most Brewing,&amp;rdquo; we delve into the process of making Maple Jack, a unique and delicious alcoholic beverage. This idea was pitched by Anna, who believed that the YouTube community would be interested in funding the project. With the support of viewers, they managed to gather the necessary funds to create this festive concoction. In this article, we will explore the fermentation process, the flavors, and the intended use of Maple Jack in a special maple eggnog recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pteris Cretica: The Ultimate Guide to Growing and Caring for the Silver Ribbon Fern</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/silver-ribbon-fern-cretan-brake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/silver-ribbon-fern-cretan-brake/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a stunning perennial evergreen fern to add to your collection of houseplants or garden, look no further than the Pteris Cretica, also known as the Cretan brake or Silver Ribbon Fern. This versatile plant is not only a great choice for indoor and outdoor landscaping, but it&amp;rsquo;s also incredibly easy to care for. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore everything you need to know about growing and caring for the Pteris Cretica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Grow Organic Persimmons in California: A Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/california-hachiya-persimmons-organic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/california-hachiya-persimmons-organic/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss how to grow organic persimmons in California. Persimmons are not only beautiful fruit trees but also highly adaptable. The fruit can be enjoyed fresh, dried, or even pickled. As an organic gardener, I am committed to growing food in a way that is healthy, safe, and sustainable. I will provide you with step-by-step instructions on how to successfully grow organic persimmons in your own backyard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Persona 5 Royal - Ann Windsor: An Exquisite Japanese Beauty</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ann-japanese-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ann-japanese-name/</guid>
      <description>Persona 5 Royal introduces players to a diverse cast of characters, each with their unique stories and backgrounds. One of the standout characters is Ann Windsor, an extraordinary individual with a captivating aura. In this article, we delve into Ann&amp;rsquo;s character, her identity, and her role in the game.
Unveiling Ann Windsor: A Blend of Cultures In Persona 5 Royal, players are introduced to Ann Windsor, a character with a fascinating blend of cultures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Your Fiddle Leaf Fig Dropping Leaves? Here&#39;s What You Need to Do ASAP!</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fig-tree-branch-is-drooping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fig-tree-branch-is-drooping/</guid>
      <description>By Claire Aiken, The Fiddle Leaf Fig Girl
It&amp;rsquo;s a common concern among fiddle leaf fig owners - why are their plants dropping leaves? If you&amp;rsquo;ve come home to find another giant leaf on the ground and your beloved fig tree looking sickly, it can be quite distressing. But fear not! There are only two main reasons why fiddle leaf figs drop leaves, and once you identify the problem, you can save your plant in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Make Wild Persimmon Trees Thrive for Deer Attraction and Winter Identification Tips</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fuyu-persimmon-deer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/fuyu-persimmon-deer/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to deer hunting, one of the key factors in attracting deer is finding areas with persimmon trees. Persimmons produce a fruit that deer find irresistible, making these trees a valuable resource for hunters. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand how to identify persimmon trees and ensure their optimal growth to yield more fruit. In this article, we will explore the characteristics of persimmon trees, how to identify them in the winter, and the steps you can take to promote their fruit production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Exotic and Hardy: Tips for Growing Bottlebrush Plants in the UK</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/like-a-saturday-bottle-brush-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/like-a-saturday-bottle-brush-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the benefits and share some tips on how to grow the beautiful and exotic bottlebrush plant, also known as Kalistamen, in the cool climate of the UK, specifically in South Wales. Bottlebrush plants are native to Australia and are surprisingly hardy, making them a great addition to any garden. We will delve into the details of growing these plants, ensuring their success even in colder temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Growing a Magnolia Tree in a Container: A Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/magnolia-tree-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/magnolia-tree-companies/</guid>
      <description>Magnolia trees are known for their beauty and elegance, but what if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a large yard or a suitable place to plant one in the ground? Is it possible to grow a magnolia tree in a container? The answer is a resounding yes! In this article, we will explore the process of growing a magnolia tree in a container and provide you with all the information you need to bring the beauty of these trees to your front porch or patio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Growing a Wonderful Pomegranate Tree: A 2-Year Update on Passion for Plants</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-silk-pomegranate-tree-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-silk-pomegranate-tree-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the growth and cultivation of the Wonderful Pomegranate tree. The Wonderful Pomegranate is a variety known for its exceptional taste and juiciness. We will explore the experience of Hannah, the host of the YouTube channel Passion for Plants, who has been nurturing this tree for the past two years in Southern California. Throughout this article, we will delve into the key points Hannah shares in the video, including the tree&amp;rsquo;s characteristics, ideal growing conditions, and maintenance tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Successfully Plant Your Johnny Appleseed Authentic Apple Tree: Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/johnny-appleseed-trees-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/johnny-appleseed-trees-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of apples and interested in growing your own apple trees? Look no further than the Johnny Appleseed Authentic Apple Tree! In this guide, we will walk you through the process of planting both bare root and container trees, ensuring that your tree has the best chance of thriving. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced gardener, follow these steps to successfully plant your Johnny Appleseed Authentic Apple Tree and enjoy the fruits of your labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What Is the Best Variety of Persimmon Tree to Grow for Backyard Gardens?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/great-wall-persimmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/great-wall-persimmon/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the best variety of persimmon tree to grow in your backyard garden. The main focus will be on a specific variety known as the Jiro or Gyro Fuyu Persimmon. We will explore why this variety is highly recommended and its unique features. By the end of this article, you will have all the information you need to decide if the Jiro Persimmon is the right choice for your garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why We Must Protect Oak Trees in Illinois: Celebrating OAKtober</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/negatives-to-oak-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/negatives-to-oak-trees/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In the state of Illinois, oak trees are not just ordinary trees; they are an integral part of our natural heritage. As we celebrate OAKtober, it is crucial to understand why we need to protect these incredible trees. Despite their significance, oak ecosystems in Illinois have dwindled down to a mere 17 due to development, invasive plants, and inadequate land management. In this article, we will explore the key reasons why oak trees are so important, the threats they face, and the measures we can take to ensure their survival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> American Persimmons: The Importance of Male Pollinators</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-pollination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/persimmon-pollination/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will discuss the significance of male pollinators for American persimmons. Many nurseries mislead customers by suggesting that certain types of American persimmons or their crosses with Japanese persimmons do not require a pollinator. However, having a male pollinator is crucial for a bountiful crop of superior persimmons. We will explore the differences between male and female persimmon flowers, demonstrate the importance of male trees in increasing fruit production, and share personal experiences and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Successfully Grow White Chiffon® Rose of Sharon (Hibiscus syriacus)</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hibiscus-syriacus-double-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hibiscus-syriacus-double-white/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to HortTube! In this article, we will discuss the beautiful and low-maintenance White Chiffon Rose of Sharon, also known as Hibiscus syriacus. This ornamental shrub is cold hardy and can grow up to 12 feet in height and eight to ten feet in width. We will explore the key points of growing and caring for this stunning plant, including its preferred sunlight exposure, ideal planting location, blooming period, and tips for maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mast Trees: Unmatched Quality and Salt Tolerance</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/are-mast-trees-salt-tolerant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/are-mast-trees-salt-tolerant/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to The Tree Planters, your go-to source for all things tree-related. In this article, we will be exploring the beauty and uniqueness of mast trees, also known as large trees and palms. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a tree lover or a landscape designer, understanding the features and qualities of different tree species can greatly enhance your gardening experience. Join us as we delve into the fascinating world of mast trees and discover why they are a top choice for any garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pomegranate Taste Test 2022: Reviewing Wonderful, Parfianka, Utah Sweet, Angel Red, Desertnyi, and More</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/parfianka/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/parfianka/</guid>
      <description>Pomegranates are not only delicious fruits but also packed with several health benefits. In this taste test, we will be reviewing different varieties of pomegranates, including Wonderful, Parfianka, Utah Sweet, Angel Red, Desertnyi, and many more. Our expert taste testers, Charles Malco, Bill Brandt, and Paul Talley, will provide their honest opinions on the flavor, seed softness, acidity, and sweetness of each variety.
Introduction: Charles Malco, a biologist and plant expert, along with his team from IV Organic, conducts a taste test featuring some of the finest pomegranate varieties in Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AU Producer Plum: A Steady Producer for Wildlife</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/au-producer-plum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/au-producer-plum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In this article, we will explore the benefits of adding the AU Producer Plum to your food plots for wildlife. Plums are a fantastic option for attracting and providing sustenance to various wildlife species. We will discuss the significance of having a diverse range of drop dates for your plants and how it can help in retaining game animals on your property. By strategically planting plums, apples, pears, and other fruits with different drop times, you can ensure a steady supply of food throughout the growing season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mexican White Oak &#39;Monterrey Oak&#39;: The Ultimate Guide to Planting and Growing</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mexican-white-oak-for-sale-near-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/mexican-white-oak-for-sale-near-me/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a beautiful and resilient tree to add to your backyard? Look no further than the Mexican White Oak, also known as the Monterrey Oak. This tree, scientifically known as Quercus polymorpha, is native to the Monterrey mountains in Mexico but has made its way to the Valverde County of Texas, gaining popularity among tree planting enthusiasts in the South. In this article, we will explore the characteristics, history, cultivation, propagation, and maintenance of the Mexican White Oak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New Orleans Pralines: A Mouthwatering Southern Delight</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/south-alabama-pecans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/south-alabama-pecans/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Welcome to South Alabama Cooking! In this article, we will be exploring the delightful world of New Orleans Pralines. Pralines are a popular candy in the South, known for their rich flavor and melt-in-your-mouth texture. Join me as I take you through the step-by-step process of making these delicious treats.
Recipe and Ingredients
To make pralines, you will need the following ingredients:
1.5 cups of granulated sugar 1.5 cups of light brown sugar 1/4 teaspoon of salt 1/4 teaspoon of cinnamon 3/4 cup of evaporated milk 1/3 cup of cane syrup First, combine the granulated sugar and light brown sugar in a pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alabama Pecan Growers Association Shares Secrets to Successful Pecan Harvest</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-tree-north-alabama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-tree-north-alabama/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a mesmerizing display of hard work and dedication, the Alabama Pecan Growers Association recently visited a local orchard to learn about the secrets behind their impeccable pecan harvest. Newberry Pecans Orchard, located in North Alabama, hosted the group and showcased their unique irrigation system and award-winning packaging. This article delves into the details of the visit, highlighting the key takeaways and the passionate individuals behind the thriving pecan industry in Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alocasia Bambino Care and Propagation: A Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/colocasia-bambino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/colocasia-bambino/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we are going to explore the care and propagation of the stunning Alocasia Bambino. This plant, also known as Colocasia Bambino, is a dwarf version of the Alocasia Amazonica and boasts beautiful narrow leaves with unique silver markings. We will dive into the details of how to care for this plant and discuss its propagation techniques.
Key Points: Alocasia Bambino is a dwarf version of the Alocasia Amazonica, with smaller leaves but thicker foliage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Quick Tip: How Often to Water Propagate Fig Tree Cuttings</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-often-to-water-propagate-fig-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-often-to-water-propagate-fig-tree/</guid>
      <description>The process of propagating fig tree cuttings can be challenging, especially when it comes to watering them. As gardeners, we want to keep the soil moist enough to prevent the cuttings from drying out, but we also need to avoid overwatering them and causing rot. In this article, we will share a simple yet effective technique for watering fig cuttings using a turkey baster. By following this method, you can ensure that your fig cuttings receive the right amount of water to thrive and grow into healthy trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Raintree Fruit Feature: Discover the Delightful Melrose Apple! A Guide to Growing and Enjoying this Ohio State Favorite</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/melrose-apple-trees-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/melrose-apple-trees-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Raintree Nursery, where we are delighted to introduce you to the enchanting and flavorful Melrose apple. In this article, we will delve into the captivating qualities of this apple variety, from its tantalizing taste to its resistance to common apple diseases. Whether you are an avid gardener or simply appreciate the delectable world of apples, the Melrose apple is sure to capture your heart.
The Captivating Flavor of Melrose Apples The Melrose apple is a true gem when it comes to taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is the Best Variety of Persimmon Tree to Grow for Backyard Gardens?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/izu-persimmon-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/izu-persimmon-tree/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for the perfect fruit tree to add to your backyard garden? Look no further than the Izu Persimmon tree! In this article, we will explore why the Izu Persimmon is the best variety of persimmon tree for your garden, its unique characteristics, and how to grow and care for it.
The Izu Persimmon tree, also known as the Jiro or Gyro Fuyu Persimmon, is a highly sought-after variety among gardeners and persimmon enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Winter Tree Damage: Identifying and Fixing Cold Damage on Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/winter-tree-damage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/winter-tree-damage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As winter begins to fade away and the warmer months approach, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for gardeners to assess the health of their trees and identify any potential damage caused by the cold weather. The winter season, especially this year, has been particularly harsh, with record-breaking cold temperatures affecting many regions of the country. In this article, we will discuss how to determine if your trees have been damaged or killed by the cold and provide steps on how to fix it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Worm-Free Kadota Fig: A Guide to Growing Delicious Figs</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/worm-free-kadota-fig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/worm-free-kadota-fig/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you interested in growing your own delicious figs? Look no further than the Kadota fig tree. In this article, we will explore the process of growing and caring for a Kadota fig tree, as well as the challenges that come with it. Join us as we delve into the world of fig trees and uncover the secrets to a bountiful harvest.
The Story of the Kadota Fig Tree The Kadota fig tree featured in this article is approximately a year and a half old and has been thriving in the Edge of Nowhere Farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 12 Amazing Facts About Oak Trees You Won&#39;t Believe</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/bur-oak-pros-and-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/bur-oak-pros-and-cons/</guid>
      <description>Oak trees are among the oldest and most widespread trees on Earth, existing long before humans. They not only provide sustenance for various animals but have also played a crucial role in human history. From building homes and creating tools to constructing strong ships, oak wood has been a valuable resource throughout time. In modern society, oak trees continue to be a vital source of raw materials, used in the production of elegant furniture, flooring materials, cosmetic creams, and even wine barrels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Successfully Grow Pomegranates in Cold Climate: A Complete Guide to Russian Pomegranate Salavatski</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardy-pomegranate-6a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/hardy-pomegranate-6a/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you interested in growing pomegranates in a cold climate? Look no further! In this article, we will provide a complete guide on how to successfully grow pomegranates, specifically the Russian Pomegranate Salavatski, in a clay soil environment. We will cover the ideal time to plant, the best techniques for planting and caring for the tree, tips on fruiting and flowering, and even a few words on taste and pest control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Martha Stewart&#39;s Delicious Nut-Filled Desserts: Linzer Tart, Peanut Butter Oatmeal Sandwich Cookies, and San Andre Cake</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/stuart-pecans-taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/stuart-pecans-taste/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Nuts are a versatile ingredient that adds texture and flavor to any recipe. Martha Stewart, the queen of home cooking, has a special fondness for nuts and loves to incorporate them into her desserts. In this episode of Martha Bakes, titled &amp;ldquo;Nuts,&amp;rdquo; Martha shares four different nut-based recipes that are sure to impress. From a delightful Linzer Tart filled with raspberry jam to decadent Peanut Butter Oatmeal Sandwich Cookies, and a beautiful San Andre Cake featuring fresh walnut flour, these desserts highlight the unique qualities of various nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Companion Planting Tips for Fruit Trees - Increase Fruit Production and Create a Beautiful Garden</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/companion-plants-for-fig-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/companion-plants-for-fig-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will explore the concept of companion planting and how it can greatly benefit your fruit trees. By strategically choosing companion plants, you can increase pollination, attract beneficial insects, and ultimately enhance the overall health and productivity of your garden. We will delve into specific examples and offer tips to help you achieve maximum success with your fruit trees.
Underplanting with Nasturtiums for Pollination
One effective technique in companion planting involves underplanting your fruit trees with flowers that attract pollinators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pomegranate Taste Test 2022: A Deep Dive into the Wonderful World of Pomegranates</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-silk-pomegranate-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-silk-pomegranate-tree/</guid>
      <description>Are you curious to explore and savor the exquisite flavors of pomegranates? Look no further. In this article, we will take you on a delightful journey of taste testing different varieties of pomegranates. Join us as we dive into the world of the red silk pomegranate tree and discover the characteristics of various pomegranate varieties. From soft and sweet to tart and tangy, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the nuances of flavor and texture that make each pomegranate unique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who Are Princess Peach&#39;s Parents? Unraveling the Mystery of KING Peach</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/king-peach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/king-peach/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Princess Peach, the beloved character from the Mario franchise, has long been recognized as a princess. However, many fans have wondered if there is a king and queen peach who rule over the Mushroom Kingdom. In this article, we dive deep into the Mario franchise and explore the history to uncover the truth about Princess Peach&amp;rsquo;s parents, shedding light on this long-standing mystery.
The Games: A Hint to the Past If you&amp;rsquo;ve played any Mario games before, you probably know that Princess Peach&amp;rsquo;s parents are not prominent characters in the series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Produce 101: A Comprehensive Guide to Pears and their Many Varieties</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/bulk-pears-produce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/bulk-pears-produce/</guid>
      <description>Pears are a popular and versatile fruit that come in many different varieties. In this article, we will explore the basics of pears, including the different types of pears, grading systems, ripening techniques, handling tips, and the best ways to use them in various culinary applications. Whether you are a pear enthusiast or simply curious about this delicious fruit, read on to learn all you need to know about pears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Building a Stunning Waterfall Table from Urban Texas Pecan Wood</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/really-large-pecan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/really-large-pecan/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of woodworking, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this challenging project that we&amp;rsquo;re about to share with you. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the process of building a unique and stunning waterfall table using urban Texas pecan wood. This project combines craftsmanship and creativity to create a one-of-a-kind piece that will surely be the centerpiece of any space.
Understanding the Waterfall Table Design
A waterfall table is a unique type of table where the grain flows seamlessly from the table surface down to the legs, creating a mesmerizing visual effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Joe Rogan Reveals Astonishing Information About Antarctica and its Mysterious Past</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/japanese-sentinel-toadstool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/japanese-sentinel-toadstool/</guid>
      <description>Antarctica, the frozen continent located at the southernmost point of our planet, has long been a source of fascination and intrigue. Its icy landscapes and extreme conditions have made it one of the most uninhabited places in the world, yet there is more to this mysterious landmass than meets the eye. In a recent episode of the Joe Rogan Experience Podcast, Joe Rogan himself, along with his guests, delves into some of the strangest and most shocking facts about Antarctica that you may not know about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making Truffle Trees for the Farm: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/inoculated-truffle-trees-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/inoculated-truffle-trees-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered how to grow truffle trees on your farm? If you&amp;rsquo;ve tried to find information on this topic, you may have realized that there isn&amp;rsquo;t much guidance available. In this article, we will walk you through the process of creating your own truffle trees, specifically the Tuber Melanosporum variety, also known as black truffle.
Truffles are a type of mycorrhizal fungi that grow on the roots of trees, forming a symbiotic relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Raintree Nursery Fruit Feature: Suncrisp Apple - A Delicious Early Ripening Apple Perfect for Northern Growers</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/suncrisp-apple-for-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/suncrisp-apple-for-storage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Raintree Nursery&amp;rsquo;s fruit feature, where we take a closer look at some of the amazing fruits grown in our nursery orchard. In today&amp;rsquo;s feature, we will be discussing the Suncrisp apple, also known as the Zestar apple. This early ripening apple is a favorite among Northern growers, thanks to its delicious flavor and ability to thrive in colder climates.
The Zestar Apple - Early Ripener and Early Bloomer The Zestar apple, classified as an early ripener and an early bloomer in bloom category one, is a variety of apple that blooms and ripens earlier than most other apple varieties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 5 Best Peach Trees for Your Garden</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/autumn-star-peach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/autumn-star-peach/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to add some delicious and beautiful peach trees to your garden? Look no further! In this article, we will go over the top 5 best peach trees that are guaranteed to delight your taste buds and enhance your garden&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic. From unique flavors to exceptional disease resistance, these trees have it all. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
1. Indian Free Peach Our number five pick is the Indian Free Peach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 5 Most Popular Crabapple Trees for Your Outdoor Living Space</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/outdoor-living-company-crabapple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/outdoor-living-company-crabapple/</guid>
      <description>Crabapple trees, originating in Asia during the 18th century, have become a beloved addition to landscapes all across the United States. These trees serve as reliable street trees and beautiful ornamental options, especially in colder climates where they can withstand harsh weather conditions. With over 30 different species and hundreds of hybrid varieties, choosing the perfect crabapple tree can be a daunting task. In this article, we will highlight the top five most popular crabapple trees that are sure to enhance your outdoor living space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> H1: How Long Does It Take for Fig Cuttings to Root?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/keep-fresh-fig-cuttings-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/keep-fresh-fig-cuttings-cool/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fig trees can be propagated from cuttings, but the process can be lengthy and uncertain. Many factors, such as variety, environmental conditions, and care, can affect the rooting time and success rate of fig cuttings. In this article, we will explore how long it typically takes for fig cuttings to root and when it might be time to consider discarding them. We will also discuss the importance of patience and provide some tips on how to increase your chances of success when propagating fig cuttings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Planting Around Utilities: How Trees and Power Infrastructure Can Coexist</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/trees-next-to-underground-transformers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/trees-next-to-underground-transformers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Many people assume that trees and utilities are incompatible and cannot coexist. However, this couldn&amp;rsquo;t be further from the truth. With proper planning and consideration, it is possible to have trees and power infrastructure in close proximity without conflicts. In this article, we will explore the key points discussed in a YouTube video by Moonlight Communications, where they shed light on the importance of planting trees near utilities and provide insightful guidelines on how to do so effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Fascinating Story Behind the Expensive Honeycrisp Apples</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/buy-candy-crisp-apple-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/buy-candy-crisp-apple-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction There&amp;rsquo;s something magical about sinking your teeth into a bright, red, and juicy apple. And when it comes to the Honeycrisp apple, the experience becomes even more extraordinary. Developed in 1960 by the University of Minnesota, the Honeycrisp apple is a unique variety that has captivated apple lovers around the world. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the fascinating story behind the Honeycrisp apple, explore the reasons for its premium price tag, and provide some alternatives for those seeking a similar taste without breaking the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 13 Fruit Trees You Can Grow in Zone 10b Backyard</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/best-fruit-trees-for-zone-10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/best-fruit-trees-for-zone-10b/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore 13 different fruit trees that you can grow in your backyard if you live in zone 10b. These trees offer a variety of fruits and are well-suited to the climate in this zone. Whether you are a seasoned gardener or a beginner, these fruit trees are relatively easy to care for and will provide you with delicious, homegrown produce. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover the best fruit trees for zone 10b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Essential Tips for Taking Care of Dracaena Plants</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/dracaena-janet-craig-in-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/dracaena-janet-craig-in-water/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dracaena plants, commonly known as Drasenas, are a popular choice among plant enthusiasts due to their vibrant foliage and low-maintenance requirements. However, to ensure the health and longevity of your Dracaena plants, it is important to follow a few essential care tips. In this article, we will provide you with five quick tips to help you successfully care for your Dracaena plants.
1. Protect Your Dracaena from Cold Temperatures All Dracaena plants are highly sensitive to cold temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> My Favorite Vegan Meat Substitute: Pecan Meat for Raw Tacos or Cheese Fake Hoagies!</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-flesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/pecan-flesh/</guid>
      <description>Are you searching for a delicious vegan alternative to meat? Look no further! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the amazing world of pecan meat and how it can be used as a versatile substitute in various dishes, including raw tacos and cheese fake hoagies. Just follow these simple steps and you&amp;rsquo;ll have a mouthwatering vegan meal in no time!
Why Pecan Meat? Pecan meat is not only a delicious and nutritious option for vegans but also a great choice for those looking to reduce their meat consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Planting Pear Trees: A Guide to What to Expect After 10 Years</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ure-pear-tree-pollination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ure-pear-tree-pollination/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In this article, we will explore the process of planting pear trees and what to expect after 10 years. Pear trees require cross-pollination, so it is crucial to plant two different varieties to ensure successful fruit production. We will discuss the planting process, including the ideal tree size, depth, and the importance of choosing the right location. Additionally, we will provide insight into the pollination process, tree care, harvesting, and storage techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **7 Mistakes to Avoid When Growing Ochlockonee Blueberries**</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ochlockonee-blueberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/ochlockonee-blueberry/</guid>
      <description>Blueberries are a delicious and nutritious fruit that is easy to grow. However, in order to be successful in growing blueberries, it is crucial to avoid making certain mistakes. In this article, we will discuss the seven most common mistakes to avoid when growing ochlockonee blueberries, a popular variety of blueberries. By following these guidelines, you can ensure a thriving blueberry garden and enjoy an abundant harvest of this sweet and tangy fruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Exotic and Resilient: Tips for Successfully Growing Bottlebrush Plants</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/spacing-bottlebrush-red-clusters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/spacing-bottlebrush-red-clusters/</guid>
      <description>Overview: In this article, we will explore the beauty and benefits of the bottlebrush plant, also known as Kalistamen. We will provide tips and guidelines for successfully growing bottlebrush plants in cool climates, specifically focusing on the UK, and in particular, South Wales. With its vibrant red clusters and hardy nature, the bottlebrush plant adds a touch of exotic elegance to any garden.
Summer Garden Tour: Before delving into the specifics of cultivating bottlebrush plants, let&amp;rsquo;s take a quick 30-second tour of our summer garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Harvesting Non-Astringent (Crunchy) Persimmons: A Guide to Proper Harvesting Techniques</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/maekawa-jiro-persimmon-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/maekawa-jiro-persimmon-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the process of harvesting non-astringent persimmons, specifically the Jiro variety. Persimmons are a delicious fruit that can be enjoyed fresh or dried, and harvesting them at the right time is crucial to ensure the best flavor and texture. We will explore the key points to keep in mind while harvesting, including the effects of frost and the importance of proper ripening. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover how to harvest non-astringent persimmons like a pro!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Soon Will a Seedling Japanese Walnut Bear Fruit?</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-soon-will-a-seedling-japanese-walnut-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-soon-will-a-seedling-japanese-walnut-bear/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to My High Desert Garden, where we explore all things related to gardening and plant cultivation. In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we will be addressing a crucial question that many gardeners often have - how long does it take for a fruit tree to bear fruit when grown from a seed? This is a topic that is frequently discussed on various platforms like YouTube, and it can be challenging to find consistent answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Care for a Dracaena Lemon Lime Plant: A Complete Guide | Gardening with Susie TLC</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/dracaena-lemon-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/dracaena-lemon-surprise/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a plant enthusiast or looking to add some greenery to your home, the Dracaena Lemon Lime plant is a beautiful and low-maintenance option. In this comprehensive care guide, we will walk you through everything you need to know about keeping your Dracaena Lemon Lime plant healthy and thriving. Join Susie from Gardening with Susie TLC as she shares her expertise and tips on caring for this stunning plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> This is the Biggest Fig I&#39;ve Ever Grown: Robert&#39;s Golden Rainbow</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/giant-yellow-fig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/giant-yellow-fig/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this video, we are going to take a closer look at one of the most remarkable fig trees ever grown. The fig tree in question is called Robert&amp;rsquo;s Golden Rainbow, and it has produced some of the largest figs ever seen. Despite being just four months old, this fig tree has already exceeded expectations with its massive fruits. Join us as we explore the unique features of this incredible fig tree and discover why it deserves a special place in any garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Scindapsus Plant Care Guide: Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/scindapsus-pictus-exotica-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/scindapsus-pictus-exotica-canada/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the world of Scindapsus plants and discuss the care and propagation of three popular varieties: Jade Satin, Exotica, and Treubii. Scindapsus plants are often compared to Pothos plants, but they have a few subtle differences that we will explore. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned plant parent or just starting out, this comprehensive guide will help you care for your Scindapsus plants and troubleshoot any issues that may arise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making Crabapple Wine at Home: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/air-conditioning-installation-crabapple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/air-conditioning-installation-crabapple/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Owning a crabapple tree comes with its perks. The beautiful blossoms in the spring and the vibrant red apples in the fall are a sight to behold. But have you ever considered making wine from these crabapples? In this article, we will guide you through the process of making crabapple wine at home, from harvesting to bottling.
Harvesting the Crabapples Harvesting crabapples is a straightforward process. All you need is a ladder, a bucket, and a pair of scissors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making Truffle Trees for the Farm - A Guide to Growing Tuber Melanosporum</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/truffle-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/truffle-trees/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Truffle trees are a fascinating and valuable addition to any farm or garden. These unique trees are infected with a type of fungus called Tuber Melanosporum, also known as black truffle. In this article, we will explore the process of growing truffle trees from scratch, including the materials needed, step-by-step instructions, and potential challenges.
Understanding Truffle Trees and Their Benefits Truffle trees are special because they are symbiotically connected to Tuber Melanosporum, a mycorrhizal fungi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Growing Self-Pollinating Persimmon Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/self-pollinating-persimmon-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/self-pollinating-persimmon-trees/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a gardener looking to add a unique and delicious fruit tree to your backyard, look no further than the persimmon tree. Not only are persimmons incredibly easy to grow, but they offer a heavenly flavor that is unlike any other fruit. In this comprehensive guide, we will take you through everything you need to know about growing persimmon trees, from selecting the right variety to caring for your tree and harvesting the delicious fruits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Class Action Lawsuit Filed Against DR Horton Builders: Nightmares in Dream Homes</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/slab-leak-detection-pecan-hill-tx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/slab-leak-detection-pecan-hill-tx/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Two families in Youngsville, Texas, are sharing their stories of living in what was supposed to be their dream homes, only to face a series of nightmares. After years of dealing with warranty issues, leaks, and mold growth, these families have taken legal action by filing a class-action lawsuit for damages against DR Horton builders. This article will delve into the details of their experiences and shed light on the ongoing lawsuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CORPSE Found Hidden In Tree Trunk: Unearthing a Celtic Treasure Trove in Wales</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/trees-fall-dig-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/trees-fall-dig-risk/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Unearthing hidden treasures often requires a combination of persistence, luck, and a passion for discovery. This was certainly the case for Mike Smith, an amateur treasure hunter, whose hobby led him to a remarkable find in south Pembrokeshire, Wales. In February 2018, while metal detecting on unexplored farmland, Smith stumbled upon something that would change his life forever. Little did he know, he had found a piece of a Celtic chariot burial, dating back over 2,000 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making Truffle Trees for the Farm - A Step-by-Step Guide to Growing Truffle Trees</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/truffle-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/truffle-tree/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Truffle trees, an essential part of any truffle farm, can be quite expensive to purchase. However, with a little knowledge and effort, you can make your own truffle trees at a fraction of the cost. In this guide, we will explore the process of creating truffle trees using the Tuber Melanosporum variety, also known as black truffles.
What are Truffle Trees?
Truffle trees are oak trees that are infected with the Tuber Melanosporum fungus, forming a symbiotic relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Magical Plum Tree: A Surprising Twist in Nature&#39;s Plan</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/plum-tree-magical-uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/plum-tree-magical-uses/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the fascinating story of a plum tree that defied the odds and transformed into an unexpected surprise in the garden. We will delve into the journey of this tree, starting from its humble beginnings and the challenges it faced, to its surprising transformation that left the gardener bewildered. So grab a cup of tea and join us as we uncover the magical tale of the plum tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tips to Keep Your Trees from Falling: Ensuring Safety and Preventing Damage</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-prevent-trees-from-dropping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/how-to-prevent-trees-from-dropping/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In recent weeks, we have witnessed the devastating impact of toppling trees causing severe damage or obstructing roads. With the combination of heavy rain and strong winds, many homeowners are left wondering about the safety of their own trees. To provide expert advice on how to assess the risk and prevent tree failures, we turned to Terry Breyer, an arborist with The Davey Tree Expert Company. In this article, we will delve into the valuable insights offered by Terry and discuss crucial steps homeowners can take to ensure the safety of their trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Moon Cactus Rot: How to Save a Rotting Cactus</title>
      <link>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-grafted-moon-cactus-shriveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plantmegreen.github.io/posts/red-grafted-moon-cactus-shriveling/</guid>
      <description>Are you a plant lover who is facing the challenge of a rotting moon cactus? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we are here to help! In this article, we will guide you through the process of saving a rotting moon cactus. Moon cacti are unique plants that rely on another chlorophyll-rich plant for nutrition, as they do not produce their own chlorophyll. They are grafted onto other cacti, and if the root stock rots, it can put the entire plant in danger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
